rameşaliyev

Computer Scientist

I'm Ramesh, a former Software Engineer from Istanbul who mostly experienced in Web Technologies. I've worked in various companies as Lead and Senior Software Engineer. Currently I'm a Computer Science student at YTU. I'm interested in AI and mostly Computer Vision.

education

Yildiz Technical University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science (2019 - 2023)

Sakarya University
Associate of Science - AS, Computer Programming (2016 - 2018)

Zeytinburnu Industrial Vocational High School High School Diploma, Electronics (2004 - 2007)

certifications

Fundamentals of Deep Learning NVIDIA, Deep Learning Institute (2021)

Data Science Math Skills Coursera, Duke University (2020)

experiences

Co-Founder & Full Stack Developer - Ecma Co. Ltd. Jun 2017 - Present

Senior Full Stack Developer - Omma Sep 2018 - Nov 2020 (2 year 3 months)

Senior Frontend Developer - Pisano Feb 2018 - Sep 2018 (8 months)

Lead Full Stack Developer - Emlakjet Jan 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Senior JavaScript Developer - Turkcell Oct 2013 - Dec 2015 (2 years 3 months) JavaScript Developer - E-NET Internet Technology Co. Jan 2013 - Sep 2013 (9 months)

Frontend Developer - Techpoint Labs Mar 2012 - Jan 2013 (11 months)

Full Stack Developer - Koridor Design Studio Feb 2009 - Mar 2012 (3 years 2 months)

links

rames.dev github.com/ramesaliyev linkedin.com/in/ramesaliyev

contact

ramesaliyev@gmail.com